Guide to the Japan International Christian University Foundation, Inc. Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Events, Programs, Series III
  - Programs
    - ICU High School in New York, 1984-1986 (Box 52, Folder 549)
    - Tree Project to Honor Birthdays, 1962-1982 (Box 52, Folder 550)
    - Tree Project to Honor Birthdays, 1983-1991 (Box 52, Folder 551)
    - Douglas MacArthur Scholarship, 1962-1963 (Box 52, Folder 552)
    - Sagamihara Masonic Education Fund, 1962-1964 (Box 52, Folder 553)
- Financial and Fundraising Records, Series IV
  Financial documents and statements
  Sample records/ transactions
  Officers' files
  Finance Committee and investment records
  Fundraising records
  - Financial Documents and Statements
    - Act of Endowment, 1949-1970 (Box 53, Folder 554)
    - Bylaws to Act of Endowment (Box 53, Folder 555)
    - Changes to Act of Endowment, Bylaws (Box 53, Folder 556)
    - Tax Exemption, New York City, 1946-1950 (Box 53, Folder 557)
    - Tax Exemption, New York State Questionnaire, 1971-1985 (Box 53, Folder 558)
    - Department of Labor, New York State, 1988 (Box 53, Folder 559)
    - JICUF Historical Budget, 1964-1980 (Box 53, Folder 560)
    - JICUF Historical Budget, 1980-1988 (Box 53, Folder 561)
    - Historical Financial Reports, 1949-1966 (Box 53, Folder 562)
    - Financial Statements, 1972-1976 Mar (Box 53, Folder 563)
    - Financial Statements - Original Copies, 1976 Apr-1980 Mar (Box 54, Folder 564)
    - Financial Statements - Original Copies, 1980 Apr-1983 Mar (Box 54, Folder 565)
    - Financial Statements - Original Copies, 1983 Apr- 1986 Mar (Box 54, Folder 566)
    - Financial Statements - Original Copies, 1986 Apr-1990 Mar (Box 54, Folder 567)
    - Financial Statements - Audited, 1946-1950 (Box 54, Folder 568)
    - Financial Statements - Audited, 1951-1965 (Box 55, Folder 569)
    - Financial Statements - Audited, 1966-1975 (Box 55, Folder 570)
    - Financial Statements - Audited, 1976-1985 (Box 55, Folder 571)
    - Financial Statements - Audited, 1986-1990 (Box 55, Folder 572)
    - Financial Statements - Audited, 1991-1995 (Box 70, Folder 773)
  - Sample records/Transactions
    - Bank Statements: Marine Midland Activity Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 55, Folder 573)
    - Marine Midland Statements of Transaction, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 574)
    - Marine Midland Bank Statements, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 575)
    - Marine Midland Bank Statements, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 576)
    - Marine Midland Cleared Checks, 1989 Apr-Jul (Box 56, Folder 577)
    - Marine Midland Cleared Checks, 1989 Aug-Nov (Box 56, Folder 578)
    - Marine Midland Cleared Checks, 1989 Dec-1990 Mar (Box 56, Folder 579)
    - Marine Midland Pension Account, 1985-1988 (Box 56, Folder 580)
    - Bank Statements - Citibank, 1988-1989 (Box 56, Folder 581)
    - Bank Statements - Citibank, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 582)
    - Donation Receipts, 1988 Apr (Box 56, Folder 583)
    - Donation Receipts, 1989 Dec (Box 56, Folder 584)
    - Donation Receipts, 1989 Dec (Box 57, Folder 585)
    - Donation Receipts, 1990 Jan (Box 57, Folder 586)
    - Subsidiaries, 1971-1981 (Box 71)
    - Receipts - Disbursements - Payroll, 1948-1949 1981-1987 1987-1990 (Box 72)
  - Officers' Files
    - Tiller, Carl M., 1980-1983 (Box 57, Folder 587)
    - Tiller, Carl M. - Treasurer, 1983-1985 (Box 57, Folder 588)
    - Cochran, Raymond, 1985-1990 (Box 57, Folder 589)
    - Shorrock, Hallam C. Jr. - Vice President for Financial Affairs, New Salary Schedule, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 590)
    - Correspondence with Tabuchi Minoru - Social Security, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 591)
  - Financial Committee and Investment Records
    - Investment and Finance Committee - JICUF Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 58, Folder 592)
    - Investment and Finance Committee, 1986-1990 (Box 58, Folder 593)
    - Divestment, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 594)
    - Finance Committee Meeting, 1977-1982 (Box 58, Folder 595-615)
    - Finance Committee Meeting, 1983-1987 (Box 59, Folder 616-629)
    - Finance Committee Meeting, 1988 Mar 9 (Box 60, Folder 630-639)
    - Investment Committee Meeting, 1988 Mar 11 (Box 60, Folder 630)
    - Finance Committee Meeting, 1988-1990 (Box 60, Folder 631-639)
    - Investment Committee, 1983-1987 (Box 60, Folder 640)
    - Investment Committee Meeting, 1986 Sep (Box 60, Folder 641)
    - Investments (Box 61, Folder 642)
    - Marine Midland Investments (Box 61, Folder 643)
    - Marinvest Report, 1987 Sep (Box 61, Folder 644)
    - Lehman Cash Management Fund Inc., 1981 Oct-1982 Jun (Box 61, Folder 645)
    - Tamblyn and Brown Contract, 1949-1950 (Box 61, Folder 646)
    - Tamblyn and Brown - Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 61, Folder 647)
    - Regional Directors Conference, 1950 (Box 61, Folder 647)
    - Tamblyn and Brown - JICU 10,000,000 Fund, 1949-1950 (Box 61, Folder 648)
    - Tamblyn and Brown - JICU 10,000,000 Fund Campaign Plan (Box 61, Folder 649)
    - Tamblyn and Brown - Fundraising Report (Box 61, Folder 650)
    - Tamblyn and Brown Legal Materials, 1949-1950 (Box 61, Folder 651)
    - Scudder Cash Investment Trust, 1981 Oct-1982 Jul (Box 62, Folder 652)
    - Stuyvesant Capital Management, 1984-1985 (Box 62, Folder 653)
    - Union Cash Management, 1981 Dec-1982 May (Box 62, Folder 654)
    - U.S.A. Treasury Bills (Box 62, Folder 655)
    - Charts for Trip to ICU, 1987 Apr (Box 62, Folder 656)
  - Fundraising
    - List of Sponsors (Box 62, Folder 657)
    - Sponsors (Deceased) (Box 62, Folder 658)
    - Sponsors - Grew, Joseph C. (Box 62, Folder 659)
    - Sponsors: A-C (Box 62, Folder 660)
    - Sponsors: D-J (Box 62, Folder 661)
    - Sponsors: K-N (Box 63, Folder 662)
    - Sponsors: O-Z (Box 63, Folder 663)
    - Men's Executive Committee: Deferred Giving Program, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 664)
    - Youth Campaign, 1949-1953 (Box 63, Folder 665)
    - Fund for the Future (Box 63, Folder 666)
    - American Express Company - Matching Gifts (Box 63, Folder 667)
    - Research, Grants, Assistance (Box 63, Folder 668)
    - Japan Studies Grant, 1986-1987 (Box 63, Folder 669)
    - Asian Studies Exchange (Box 63, Folder 670)
    - Intercultural Offerings (Box 63, Folder 671)
    - Urban Forest Plan (Box 63, Folder 672)
    - Peace Studies (Box 63, Folder 673)
    - Contributions, 1948-1977 (Box 64, Folder 674)
    - Contributions, 1977-1982 (Box 64, Folder 675)
    - Development Fund, Special Gift Fund (Box 64, Folder 676)
    - Financial Statements (Box 64, Folder 677)
    - Anderson Arthur and Company (Box 64, Folder 678)
    - Aquinas Fund, 1961-1974 (Box 64, Folder 679)
    - Aquinas Fund, 1974-1981 (Box 64, Folder 680)
    - Calder Foundation (Box 64, Folder 681)
    - Chesebrough-Pond's Inc. (Box 64, Folder 682)
    - The Clark Foundation (Box 64, Folder 683)
    - Chicago Bridge and Iron Foundation (Box 64, Folder 684)
    - Jenks, James L. Jr. Foundation (Box 64, Folder 685)
    - McKnight Foundation (Box 64, Folder 686)
    - JDR 3rd Fund (Box 64, Folder 687)
    - Annual Report- Rejection Letters (Box 64, Folder 688)
    - Yale University, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 689)
    - Oversize Portfolio: Campaign Posters - Tenth Anniversary
- Publications/Photographs, Series V
  Newsletters
  Radio Scripts
  Brochures
  Articles and essays about ICU
  Photographs
  - Newsletters
    - "Campaign Staff Notes", 1949 Oct -1951 Mar (Box 65, Folder 690)
    - "Latest News from ICU", 1965-1980 (Box 65, Folder 691)
    - "News and Notes", 1981-1989 (Box 65, Folder 692)
    - "News and Notes" - Alumni Bios (Box 65, Folder 693)
    - "Newsletters", 1948-1951 (Box 65, Folder 694)
    - "ICU News", 1963-1967 (Box 65, Folder 695)
  - Radio Scripts
    - "Minute Messages" (Box 65, Folder 696)
    - "Responding Responsibly" (Box 65, Folder 697)
  - Brochures
    - Printed Brochures (Box 65, Folder 698)
  - Articles About ICU
    - "The Cutting Edge of International Christian University" by Jeanne Shelton, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 699)
    - "Education for International Education at ICU" by Jeanne Shelton, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 699)
    - "The Idea was Reconciliation" by Jeanne Shelton, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 699)
    - "International Christian University" by Elizabeth Gray Vining, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 699)
    - "JICU - A Bridge of Understanding" by Betty Gray and Jeanne Shelton, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 699)
    - "JICU - Thirty Five Years of Pioneering" by Jeanne Shelton, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 699)
    - "Leadership for Service", 1979 (Box 65, Folder 699)
    - "The Prewar Legacy and Postwar Epiphany of International Christian University" by Hallam C. Shorrock, Jr., 1993 (Box 65, Folder 699)
    - "Three Decades of Building Friendships", 1979 (Box 65, Folder 699)
    - "University for a New World" by Charles H. Germany, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 699)
    - "A University with a World View", 1979 (Box 65, Folder 699)
    - "ICU - Its Christian Challenge to the Intellect, 1965 Mar 12 (Box 65, Folder 700)
    - "Navy Chaplains Bulletin", 1952 Winter (Box 66, Folder 701)
    - Japan Today (Box 66, Folder 702)
    - New World Outlook, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 703)
    - "The Values Project at ICU", 1963 (Box 66, Folder 704)
    - Editorials (Box 66, Folder 705)
    - Newspaper Clippings (Box 66, Folder 706)
    - "The Japan ICU Foundation, Inc. and the JICUF Endowment, Inc. formerly known as The Japan International Christian University Foundation, Inc. - An Overview 1946-2004" by Delores J. Roeder, ca.2004 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - "Ruth Louise Miller - Woman of Faith and Dedication" Issues of ICU Volume 7 by Delores J. Roeder, 2003 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Photographs
    - Historical (Box 67, Folder 707)
    - Historical (Box 67, Folder 708)
    - First Commencement, 1957 Mar 3 (Box 67, Folder 709)
    - Alumni Visit, 1969 Jan (Box 67, Folder 710)
    - Board of Directors, 1970 Jun 4 (Box 67, Folder 711)
    - Board Meeting, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 712)
    - Ruth Miller Retirement Dinner, 1983 Jan (Box 67, Folder 713)
    - Foundation Staff, 1985 (Box 67, Folder 714)
    - Ruth Miller Memorial Service at ICU, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 714A)
    - Miscellaneous groups and events (Box 67, Folder 715)
    - Miscellaneous groups and events (Box 67, Folder 716)
    - Negatives (Box 67, Folder 717)
    - Visitors (Box 67, Folder 718)
    - Women's Committee (Box 67, Folder 719)
    - Women's Committee (Box 67, Folder 720)
    - Women's Committee - New Jersey, 1977 Apr (Box 67, Folder 721)
    - Borton, Hugh (Box 68, Folder 722)
    - Boulding, Kenneth (Box 68, Folder 723)
    - Brunner, Emil (Box 68, Folder 724)
    - Chichibu, Setsuko (Box 68, Folder 725)
    - Cogswell, James A. (Box 68, Folder 726)
    - Diffendorfer, Ralph (Box 68, Folder 727)
    - Espy, R.H. Edwin (Box 68, Folder 728)
    - Gerhard, Robert H. (Box 68, Folder 729)
    - Gray, Betty (Box 68, Folder 730)
    - Gregory, Paul R. (Box 68, Folder 731)
    - Grew, Joseph C. (Box 68, Folder 732)
    - Hatfield, Mark (Box 68, Folder 733)
    - Ichimada, Hisato (Box 68, Folder 734)
    - Kanda, Tateo (Box 68, Folder 735)
    - MacArthur, Douglas (Box 68, Folder 736)
    - MacLean, John A. (Box 68, Folder 737)
    - Miller, Ruth (Box 68, Folder 738)
    - Murphy, Robert (Box 68, Folder 739)
    - Nakagawa, Hideyasu (Box 68, Folder 740)
    - Owada, Yasuyuki (Box 68, Folder 741)
    - Peet, Margot (Box 68, Folder 742)
    - Read, David H.C. (Box 68, Folder 743)
    - Reichauer, Edwin (Box 68, Folder 744)
    - Rickey, Branch (Box 68, Folder 745)
    - Riggs, (Mrs. Arad) (Box 68, Folder 746)
    - Rockefeller, John D. (Box 68, Folder 747)
    - Shriver, Donald (Box 68, Folder 748)
    - Sibley, (Mrs. Harper) (Box 68, Folder 749)
    - Sinoto, Yosito (Box 68, Folder 750)
    - Smith, John Coventry (Box 68, Folder 751)
    - Sockman, Ralph W. (Box 68, Folder 752)
    - Tabuchi, Minoru (Box 68, Folder 753)
    - Takahashi, Tane (Box 68, Folder 754)
    - Vining, Elizabeth (Box 68, Folder 755)
    - Watanabe, Yasuo (Box 68, Folder 756)
    - Yuasa, Hachiro (Box 68, Folder 757)
    - Yuasa, Kyozo (Box 68, Folder 758)
- ICU Buildings, Blueprints, and Property, Series VI
  The materials in this series are arranged as listed.
  - Japan's Model Library, 1960 (Box 69, Folder 759)
  - ICU Golf Course, 1964 Oct 3 (Box 69, Folder 760)
  - Dedication of Science Hall, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 761)
  - Dedication of Seabury Memorial Chapel, 1959 (Box 69, Folder 762)
  - The Campus "Pilot Plan" (Box 69, Folder 763)
  - Campus Land, 1967 Nov 18 (Box 69, Folder 764)
  - Blueprints (Box 69, Folder 765)
  - Campus Photos (Box 69, Folder 766)
  - Scrapbook Compiled by R. Miller (Box 69, Folder 767)
- Addendum, 1954-2015; Series VII
  - Official Documents and Minutes
    - Board mailings
      - Mailing, 1998 Jan (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Mailing, 1998 Feb (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - Mailing, 1998 Apr (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - Mailing, 1998 May (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - Mailing, 1998 July (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - Mailing, 1998 Sept (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - Mailing, 1998 Nov (Box 75, Folder 7)
      - Mailing, 1998 Dec (Box 75, Folder 8)
      - Mailing, 1999 Feb (Box 75, Folder 9)
      - Mailing, 1999 Jul (Box 75, Folder 10)
      - Mailing, 1999 Aug (Box 75, Folder 11)
      - Mailing, 1999 Sep (Box 75, Folder 12)
      - Mailing, 1999 Nov (Box 75, Folder 13)
      - Mailing, 1999 Dec (Box 75, Folder 14)
      - Mailing, 2000 Feb (Box 75, Folder 15)
      - Mailing, 2000 Mar (Box 75, Folder 16)
      - Mailing, 2000 Apr (Box 76, Folder 17)
      - Mailing, 2000 May (Box 76, Folder 18)
      - Mailing, 2000 Jul (Box 76, Folder 19)
      - Mailing, 2000 Sep (Box 76, Folder 20)
      - Mailing, 2000 Nov (Box 76, Folder 21)
      - Mailing, 2000 Dec (Box 76, Folder 22)
      - Mailing, 2001 Jan (Box 76, Folder 23)
      - Mailing, 2001 Mar (Box 76, Folder 24)
      - Mailing, 2001 May (Box 76, Folder 25)
      - Mailing, 2001 Jun (Box 76, Folder 26)
      - Mailing, 2001 Nov (Box 76, Folder 27)
      - Mailing, 2002 Mar (Box 76, Folder 28)
      - Mailing, 2002 Aug (Box 76, Folder 29)
      - Mailing, 2002 Nov (Box 76, Folder 30)
      - Mailing, 2004 Feb (Box 76, Folder 31)
    - Legal documents
      - JICUF Incorporation, 2000 (Box 77, Folder 32)
      - JICUF By-Laws, 2009 (Box 77, Folder 33)
      - JICUF Endowment Incorporation, 2000 (Box 77, Folder 34)
      - JICUF Endowment By-Laws, 2009 (Box 77, Folder 35)
      - JICUF Early Legal Documents, 1954-1997 (Box 77, Folder 36)
      - Memo of Understanding between JICUF and ICU, 1996-2001 (Box 77, Folder 37)
    - Minutes
      - Miscellaneous Board Minutes, 1991-1996 (Box 77, Folder 38)
      - JICUF Board Meeting, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 39)
      - JICUF Board Meeting, 1999 (Box 77, Folder 40)
      - JICUF Board Meeting, 2000 (Box 77, Folder 41)
      - JICUF Trustees' Meeting, 2001 (Box 77, Folder 42)
      - JICUF Trustees' Meeting, 2003 Jan (Box 75, Folder 43)
      - JICUF Trustees' Meeting, 2003 Sept (Box 77, Folder 44)
      - JICUF Trustees' Meeting, 2004 Mar (Box 77, Folder 45)
      - JICUF Trustees' Meeting, 2004 Sept (Box 77, Folder 46)
      - JICUF Trustees' Meeting, 2005 Mar (Box 77, Folder 47)
      - JICUF Trustees' Meeting, 2005 Sept (Box 77, Folder 48)
      - JICUF Trustees' Meeting, 2006 Sept (Box 77, Folder 49)
      - JICUF Trustees' Meeting, 2007 Mar (Box 77, Folder 50)
      - JICUF Trustees' Meeting, 2007 Sept (Box 77, Folder 51)
      - JICUF Trustees' Meeting, 2008 Mar (Box 78, Folder 52)
      - JICUF Trustees' Meeting, 2009 Mar (Box 78, Folder 53)
      - JICUF Trustees' Meeting, 2009 Sept (Box 78, Folder 54)
      - JICUF Trustees' Meeting, 2011 (Box 78, Folder 54B)
      - JICUF Trustees' Meeting, 2012 March (Box 84, Folder 1)
      - JICUF Trustees' Meeting, 2012 September (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - JICUF Trustees' Meeting, 2013 March (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - JICUF Trustees' Meeting, 2013 September (Box 84, Folder 4)
      - JICUF Trustees' Meeting, 2014 March (Box 84, Folder 5)
      - JICUF Trustees' Meeting, 2014 September (Box 84, Folder 6)
      - JICUF Trustees' conference call meeting, 2014 November (Box 84, Folder 7)
      - JICUF Trustees' Meeting, 2015 March (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Organization and Personnel Records/Correspondence
    - JICUF/ICU history
      - Advancement History, 2009 (Box 78, Folder 55)
      - Articles about ICU, 1951-1992 (Box 78, Folder 55A)
      - JICUF Scrapbook (Box 78, Folder 55B)
      - Mitaka Study Center Demonstration, 1969 (Box 78, Folder 56)
      - General Background of Japan Student Movement (Box 78, Folder 58)
      - Student Confrontations at ICU (Box 78, Folder 58)
      - History of the Women's Committee, 2000 (Box 78, Folder 59)
      - Miscellaneous ICU History (Box 78, Folder 60)
    - JICUF organization
      - Legal correspondence
        - Re. re-organization preparations, 1999 (Box 78, Folder 61)
        - Re. re-organization proposal to Board of Directors, 1999 (Box 78, Folder 62)
        - Re. solicitation materials, 2000 (Box 78, Folder 63)
        - Re. re-organization; by-laws and incorporation documents, 2000 (Box 78, Folder 64)
        - Re. IRS regulations, 2000 (Box 78, Folder 65)
        - IRS Correspondence, 2001 (Box 78, Folder 66)
      - Strategic planning
        - Long Range Strategic Plan 2000-2001 (Box 78, Folder 67)
        - Long Range Strategic Plan 2003-2004 (Box 78, Folder 68)
        - Long Range Strategic Plan 2006-2007 (Box 78, Folder 69)
        - Long Range Strategic Plan 2009-2010 (Box 79, Folder 70)
        - Stakeholder Perception Report, 2009 (Box 79)
      - Report letters
        - JICUF President's Letters, 2003-2011 (Box 79, Folder 72)
    - JICUF correspondence
      - Resumes/CVS of Board of Directors Candidates, 2000 (Box 79, Folder 73)
      - Ruth Miller, 1955-1973 (Box 79, Folder 74)
      - Yale YDS Library Archives, re. Margot Sherman Peet (Box 79, Folder 75)
    - Re. Othmer estate
      - Donald and Mildred Othmer Photographs (Box 79, Folder 76)
      - Will of Donald Othmer and other legal documents, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 77)
      - Affadavit of Charlles F. Gibbs, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 78)
      - Memo in Support of Motion for Dismissal, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 79)
      - Last Will Testament of Mildred Othmer, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 80)
      - Estate of Mildred Othmer, 2003 (Box 79, Folder 81)
      - Legal Correspondence, JICUF Treasurer, Raymond Cochrane, re. Othmer, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 82)
      - Donald Frederick and Mildred Topp Othmer, 1999 (Box 80, Folder 83)
      - Photographic Tribute Don and Mid: A Closer Look at the Othmers (Box 80, Folder 84)
      - Donald Othmer, Board Member, 1970-1988 (Box 80, Folder 85)
      - Donald Othmer, Men's Committee Member, 1968-1991 (Box 80, Folder 86)
      - Othmer Library Dedication, 2000 (Box 80, Folder 87)
      - Othmer Chair Correspondence, 1997-2001 (Box 80, Folder 88)
      - Othmer Professorship, Science, Technology Society, 1996-1999 (Box 80, Folder 89)
      - Donald and Mildred Othmer, Press (Box 80, Folder 90)
      - Donald and Mildred Othmer, Clippings (Box 80, Folder 91)
      - Jiro Mizuno's Othmer file (Box 80, Folder 92)
      - Othmer Estate Correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box 80, Folder 93)
    - ICU organization
      - Accreditation, 1995-2002 (Box 80, Folder 94)
      - Strategy
        - Conditions, Possibilities and Recommendations document, 1947 (Box 80, Folder 95)
        - ICU Self Study and Committee Draft Report, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 96)
        - ICU Self Study and Committee Report, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 97)
        - On the C in ICU (Box 80, Folder 97A)
        - Twenty-first Century ICU Forum Report, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 98)
        - ICU Self-study and Long Range Planning, 1990s (Box 81, Folder 99)
        - ICU Self-study and Long Range Planning (Box 81, Folder 100)
        - Concerning the Ideals of ICU, 1967-2010 (Box 81, Folder 101)
        - ICU Self-Study Owada, 2001 (Box 81, Folder 102)
        - ICU Learning Program, 2001 (Box 81, Folder 103)
    - ICU correspondence
      - ICU Presidents Reports to JICUF, 1992-1996 (Box 81, Folder 104)
  - Events, Programs
    - Anniversaries
      - 50th Anniversary Celebration, 1999 (Box 81, Folder 105)
    - Program proposals
      - ICU's Basic Plan for Academic Reform, 2005 (Box 81, Folder 106)
      - ICU-Nanjing University Project Plan, 2006 (Box 81, Folder 107)
      - Proposal to Strengthen Internationalism at ICU, 2008 (Box 81, Folder 108)
      - Graduate School Reform, 2007-2008 (Box 81, Folder 109)
  - Financial and Fundraising Records
    - JICUF Combined Annual Financial Reports, 2001-2011 (Box 82, Folder 110)
    - JICUF Endowment Investment Policies and Guidelines, 2011 (Box 82, Folder 111)
    - JICUF Financial Statements, 1992-1994 (Box 82, Folder 112)
    - JICUF Financial Statements, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 113)
    - JICUF Financial Statements, 1996 (Box 82, Folder 114)
    - JICUF Financial Statements, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 115)
    - JICUF Financial Statements, 1998 (Box 82, Folder 116)
    - JICUF Financial Statements, 1999 (Box 82, Folder 117)
    - Finance Committee Mailing, re. Scudder Investments, 2000 (Box 82, Folder 118)
    - JICUF Financial Statements, 2000 (Box 82, Folder 119)
    - JICUF Endowment Inc., Financial Statements, 2001 (Box 82, Folder 120)
    - JICUF and Affiliate, Financial Statements, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 121)
    - JICUF and Affiliate, Financial Statements, 2002-2003 (Box 82, Folder 122)
    - JICUF and Affiliate, Financial Statements, 2003-2004 (Box 82, Folder 123)
    - JICUF and Affiliate, Financial Statements, 2004-2005 (Box 82, Folder 124)
    - JICUF and Affiliate, Financial Statements, 2005-2006 (Box 82, Folder 125)
    - JICUF and Affiliate, Financial Statements, 2006-2007 (Box 82, Folder 126)
    - Munns Dobbins, Proposal to serve as independent auditors, 2007 (Box 83, Folder 128)
    - JICUF and Affiliate, Financial Statements, 2008-2009 (Box 83, Folder 128)
    - JICUF and Affiliate, Financial Statements, 2009-2010 (Box 83, Folder 129)
    - JICUF and Affiliate, Audit Committee Meeting, 2010 (Box 83, Folder 130)
    - JICUF and Affiliate, Financial Statements, 2010-2011 (Box 83, Folder 131)
    - Financial reports on funds received by Japan ICU, 2012-2014 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - JICUF and Affiliate, Financial Statements, 2011-2014 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Publications
    - JICUF
      - "A New Leaf" Foundation Newsletter, 2002-2006 (Box 83, Folder 132)
      - "A New Leaf" Foundation Newsletter, 2007-2011 (Box 83, Folder 133)
      - "From Swords to Plowshares, ICU: The First Ten Years", n.d. (Box 83, Folder 134)
      - JICUF, Inc. Annual Reports, 2002-2004 (Box 83, Folder 135)
      - JICUF, Inc. Annual Reports, 2004-2005 (Box 73)
      - JICUF, Inc. Annual Reports, 2005-2010 (Box 83, Folder 136)
      - JICUF, Inc. Annual Reports, 2011/2012 - 2013/2014 (Box 84, Folder 11)
      - The JICF, Inc. An Overview 1946-2004 by Delores Roeder (Box 83, Folder 137)
      - ICU Photobook, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 138)
      - ICU "The First Ten Years", 1959 (Box 83, Folder 139)
      - JICUF Brochures, 1950-1974 (Box 83, Folder 140)
    - ICU
      - ICU Gazette, 1997-1999 (Box 83, Folder 141)
      - An ICU Photobook, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 142)
      - Brochures, 2014, no date (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Monographs
      - International Christian University: An Adventure in Christian Higher Education in Japan by Charles W. Iglehart, 1964 (Box 84, Folder 12)
      - Hachiro Yuasa - The Hopes and Challenges of a Christian Educator in Japan by Kiyoko Takeda Cho, 2008 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - ICU Buildings, Blueprints, and Property
    - Dormitory Blueprints and Planning, 2005-2007 (Box 83, Folder 143)
    - ICU Japan Campus, 2011 (Box 83, Folder 144)